Guide to the W. Sterling Cole papers, [ca. 1935-1957]
Cole, W. Sterling papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
W. Sterling Cole papers, [ca. 1935-1957]
2081
W. Sterling(William Sterling), Cole 1904-1987.
42 linear ft.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Representative Cole's papers, which pertain almost exclusively to his years in the U.S. House of Representatives.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Congressman, New York 37th District, 1935-1944, 1953-1957, 39th District, 1945-1952; Director General, International Atomic Energy Agency, Vienna, 1957-1961.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Representative Cole's papers, which pertain almost exclusively to his years in the U.S. House of Representatives, include correspondence, copies of proposed bills, and newspaper clippings concerning the Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, the Committee on Armed Services, and the Naval Affairs Committee; numerous letters from constituents expressing opinions on specific legislation, presidential appointments, foreign affairs, and other issues and letters concerning pensions, workmen's compensation and other claims, appointments to the U.S. Military, Naval, and Air Force Academies, and immigration cases. Also, correspondence with the Republican Party organization and individuals concerning Congressional district campaigns and elections; letters to and from constituents and local officails pertaining to federal reimbursements for damages suffered in the 1935 flood, and inquiries and criticisms regarding flood control proposals of the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers; pamphlets issued by special interest groups; mimeographed newsletters of local Republican groups, printed campaign materials, and voters' lists; and personal papers and farm accounts, Bath, Steuben County.
Also, 37 pp. transcript of oral history interview with W. Sterling Cole, conducted by Charles T. Morrissey, August 24, 1978.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cole, W. Sterling1904-1987.; Morrissey, Charles T.; Republican Party (N.Y.); Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); United States Air Force Academy.; United States Military Academy.; United States Naval Academy.; United States.Congress.House.; United States.Congress.Joint Committee on Atomic Energy.; United States.Congress.House.Committee on Armed Services.; United States.Congress.House.Committee on Naval Affairs.; United States.Army.Corps of Engineers.
Subjects:
Veterans'--Medical care.; Old age pensions--Law and legislation.; Survivors' benefits.; Pensions, Military.; Workers' compensation--United States.; Emigration and immigration law--United States.; Electioneering.; Elections--United States.; Elections--New York (State); Politics, Practical.; Floods--New York (State); Flood control--New York (State); Agriculture--Accounting.; Farm management--New York (State)--Steuben County.; Politicians.
Places:
United States--Politics and government.; New York (State)--Politics and government.; Steuben County (N.Y.)--Politics and government.
Form and Genre Terms:
Oral histories.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Congressional Related Materials, 1928-1957
  - Campaigns and Elections, 1928-1956
    - Campaign and election material, 1950, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Balcolm, Ben, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Secretaries Club, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - School Seniors 1944 Americans Creed, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Grange Lists 1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Sightseeing 78 Congress, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Invitations 78th Congress 1st, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Perry, John, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Penny, Charlie, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Latham, J. C., Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Lounsberry, Stephen 1940, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Lounsberry, Stephen 1936-1939, 1936-1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Morgan, Lawrence, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Miller, William, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Bowlby, Thomas B., Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Convention 1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Letters re Primary 1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Primary Results 1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - General Election Results 1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Contribution Campaign 1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Primary Petitions correspondence re, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Congratulations - 1944 Primary and General Elections, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Committee Men replies form letter 1943, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Underhill, W. Allen, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Endorsements 1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Vacancy Committee 1946, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Republican State Chairman, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Peterson, Dutton S., 1942-1944, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Campaign 1950, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Committeemen misc. correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 1949 Senatorial, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - John Young, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Schuyler Co. Special Group, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Committeemen misc. correspondence 1950, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Speeches, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Campaign Expenditures & Contributions, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Congratulations - 1950 Election, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Congratulations 1950, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Rep. St. Cole N.Y. 1928, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Committee Replies Marshall Plan Military training, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Invitations 78th 2nd, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Contributions and Expenditures 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Contributions and Disbursements 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Campaign 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Presidential Elector, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Campaign Letters 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Campaign 1948 (Primaries); Letters from District, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Congratulations 1948 Primary General, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Endorsements Primary 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Congratulations 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 1948 Republican National Convention, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - General Election Returns 1946, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Peterson, Dutton S., 1946, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - 39th District Representatives, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Labor, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Primary Petitions 1946, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Congratulations General Election 1946, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - General Election Correspondence 1946, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - White, T. Clifton; Young, J. D.; Allen, Paul, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Vacancy Committee 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Presidential Elector, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - General Election 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Campaign 1946 Contributions and Expenses, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Shaw, Stanley C., Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Campaign 1946 Primary Results, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Primary 1946 Corres., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Congratulations Primary 1946, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Commendation Letters 1946 Primary Assistance, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Committee Old Lists, Date Unknown (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - 1951 - New County Committee Lists, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Congressional committees on which Cole served, 1949
    - Defense Coordination Act' or 'National Security Act', Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
    - Letters from Sullivan, J. L. (Acting Secretary of the Navy) to Andrews, W. G. (Chairman of Committee on Armed Services, House of Representatives) on specific bills concerning the military, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HR3471 - to lease (war?) material, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Armed Forces Staff, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Portrait of C. Vinson, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - HR663 and HR539 - Officer Retirement, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Unification of Military - a.t. Allen M. Shinn, Commander, U.S. Navy, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - HR2537 and HR2536 - Armed Services Promotion Bills, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Post Exchange and Ship's Stores - (inquiry into corruption), Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Pay Readjustment in Military, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - House Gymnasium Committee, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Armed Services Committee, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
    - Uniform Code of Military Justice, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Admiral Penfield on the 'Revolt of the Admirals' (1949), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Unification of Military, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - H-Bomb, Date Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Atomic Energy Fellowships (CU, et al), 1949-05-25-1949-06-10 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Committees, Date Unknown
    - Photos of Able Day and Baker Day Bomb explosions on Bikini Island, Date Unknown (Box 6, Folder 1-8)
    - Atomic Energy Commission - 81st Congress, Date Unknown (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - HR 2537 - Army/Navy promotions, Date Unknown (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Naval Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 6, Folder 11-14)
    - Naval Affairs - 'Unification' Bill, Date Unknown (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - H Res (House Resolution) 53 - Committee to Investigate Price and Rationing in Military, Date Unknown (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 76th-81st Congress legislation and correspondence, 1939-1951, 1939-1953
    - 76th Congress legislation, 1939-1941 (Box 20)
    - 76th Congress legislation, 1939-1941 (Box 21)
    - 76th Congress correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 22)
    - 77th Congress correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 23)
    - 77th Congress legislation A-J, 1941-1943 (Box 24)
    - 77th Congress legislation, 1941-1943 (Box 25)
    - 77th Congress legislation J-W, 1941-1943 (Box 26)
    - 78th Congress legislation, 1943-1945 (Box 27)
    - 78th Congress legislation, 1943-1945 (Box 28)
    - 78th Congress, 1943-1945 (Box 29)
    - 79th Congress, 1945-1947 (Box 30)
    - 80th Congress legislation, 1947-1949 (Box 31)
    - 81st Congress legislation, 1949-1951 (Box 32)
    - 81st Congress legislation, 1949-1951 (Box 33)
  - 82nd and 83rd Congress legislation, 1951-1955, 1951-1955
    - 82nd Congress legislation, 1951-1953 (Box 34)
    - 82nd Congress legislation, 1951-1953 (Box 35)
    - 82nd Congress legislation, 1951-1953 (Box 36)
    - For the relief of Manikowski, Rufin, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - PL (Private law) 21 - for the relief of Takako Niina, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - PL 168 - for the relief of Lauri Allan Torni, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HR1240 - training of candidates for appointment as nurses in military services, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HR2066 - wine production, recodify/improve requirements of Internal Revenue Law, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HR2695 - Method of payment to referees in bankruptcy court, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HR3066 - naval aid to Republic of China, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - HR3366 - conditions for accepting transmittal mail by Postmaster General, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - HR4202 - amendment to Missing Persons Act, to provide benefits to certain Philippine Scouts, letter; Rev. John E. Duffy 6/17/53 letter enclosed in Clarence H. Olsen's (to wsc ), Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - HR4905 - amendment to Atomic Energy Act of 1946, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - HR5099 - development of water power of Niagara Falls and - River, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - HR5304, HR2521, PL239 - to permit members of armed forces to elect certain contingency options and other purposes, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - HR5474 - rotation among armed services of Chairman of Joint Chiefs of Staff, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - HR6305 - amendment to Atomic Energy Act, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - HR7844 - amendment to National Security Act of 1947, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - HR7285 - amendment to Naval Act of 1921, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - HR7287 - prohibit shipment or use in interstate commerce of motor vehicles not equipped with a device to prevent being driven faster than 65 mph, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - HR5475 - provide entertainment allowance to chaplain of USMA and USNA (superseded by HR8156), Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - HR8184 - Legion of Merit award to Maj. Holohan, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - HR8861 - establishment of local self-government at Oak Ridge, Tennessee and Richmond, Virginia, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - HR8862 - Amendment to Atomic Energy Act of 1946, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - HR8967 - create Assistant Secretary of Defense, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - HR9489 - Watson, Raymond D. vs. U.S. to be heard at U.S. District Court, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - HR9757 - to amend the Atomic Energy Act of 1946, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - PL 241 - Manikowski, Rufin, considered to be born in Germany); PL21 - Takako Niina, considered to be natural-born alien child of Mr. & Mrs. Harry Romanki; PL2168 Lauri Allan Torni - admitted to U.S., Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - HR5304 - Uniformed Services Contingency Option Act of 1953, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - HR6389 - amendment to National Labor Relations Act, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - HR5133 - liberalize requirements for appointment in Nursing Service of Virginia, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - HR5132 - amend U.S. Code relating to Congressional Investigations, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - HR8189 - to provide loans for members of Armed Forces, who are entitled to National Service Life Insurance dividend Veterans Comm., Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - HR5114 - to Amend Legislative Reorganization Act of 1946, and two more staff members to Armed Services Committee, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - HR5096 - repeal authority of Secretary of Navy and Secretary of Army to nominate certain men and cadets to Academy, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - HR5061 - Amendment to Uniform Code of Military Justice, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - HR4626 - to Amend U.S. Code relative to Congressional Investigations, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - HR3710 - Director of Census Bureau to furnish information on Town of Catlin, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - HR1707 - Character Education, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - HR1109 - Relief of F. J. Cleary, U. S. Navy, Retired, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - HR1039 - amendment to National Security Act of 1947, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - H Res 387 - 2 additional staff members to House Armed Services Commission, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - H.J. Res 168 - amendment to Constitution relative to appointment of members of Supreme Court, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - H. Con. Res. 169 - Disarmament, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Cole-Ives Amendment to Defense Production Act of 1950, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - HR6807 - expand certain National Cemeteries, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - H. Con. Res 217 - Disarmament, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - HR3114 - Duty-Retired Officers, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - HR1793 - Lt. John T. McDermott, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - HR1682 - Glenn Curtiss Memorial (includes also: "Flying Pioneers at Hammondsport, NY 1904-14" pamphlet), Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - HR7635 - Armed Forces Leave, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - HR1522 - Tax on Public Properties, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - HR1521 - Annuity plan for beneficiaries of members of Armed Services, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - HR1523 - Dental Care - Navy, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - HR4388 - Naval Retiring Board, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - HR4953 - Naval Vessels - allocation of work between private and government owned shipyards, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - HR4208 - amend Section 251 of Internal Revenue Code (Philippines), Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - HR1106 - for the relief of Arrindell, A. Y. M., Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - HR4341 - For the relief of Dunn, W. H., Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - HR7164 - for the relief of Ronsetos, Peter, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Pvt. Bill - Skillman, John H., Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - HR6932 - Suprenant, Mrs. Margaret, Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - HR6013 - Chammah, Mr. I. M., Date Unknown (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - 83rd and 84th Congress legislation, 1953-1957, 1953-1957
    - HR934 - for the relief of Hirsch, Emmy R. (Mrs.), Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HR935 - for the relief of Monnell, Marion J. (Mrs.), Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HR5383 - for the relief of Webster, Betty W. (Mrs.), Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HR9935 - for the relief of Kresge, Erika K. F. (Mrs.), Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HR78 - rewards for illegal introduction/manufacture of Atomic Weapons, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HR79 - detail of certain officers of Armed Forces retired with full pay, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HR1777 - Amendment to Atomic Energy Act of 1954, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - HR3413 - Amendment to Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (patents), Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - HR4053 - Amendment to Agricultural Adjustment Act of 1958, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - HR4835 - Refund for tax on Gas for farm equipment, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - HR4914 - increase milk allowance in military ration, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - HR5788 - promotion/elimination of women officers, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - HR5961 - allow members of Armed Forces to designate Eastern Orthodox faith as religious preference, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - HR6328 - exempt from duty certain films imported to Puerto Rico, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - HR7360 - purchase merchant vessel and convert to atomic engine, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - HR9743 - development of atomic energy reactors, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - HR9802 - amendment to Atomic Energy Act of 1954, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - HR11242 - amendment to Atomic Energy Act of 1954, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - H Con. Res - proposing an Atlantic Exploratory Convention, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - H Res 23 - page matron supervises housing welfare of pages of the House, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - H. J. Res.217 - Authorizes/Requests President to fly the flag at certain service posts during daylight hours, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - H.J.Res 483 - Compensation of Staff Director of J.C.A.E., Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - HR6216 - Amendment to Social Security Act - (editorial included - see also HR13; 83rd Congress ), Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence re: HR6216 (Outside District), Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - H.Con.Res.6 - Chapel facilities for Members of Congress and families, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - H.Con.Res.93 - U.S. Congressional appeal to world for crusade for peace and freedom, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - H.Res.160 - payment for telephone service for House members, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - H.Con.Res.228 - Felicitation and Congratulations to NY State and its Board of Regents, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - HR1230 - Increase personal income tax exemption and additional exemption for spouse, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - HR1231 - prohibit bail by subversive individuals or organizations, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - HR1231 - amendment to Social Security Act, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - HR1233 - provide medal for valor for U.S.A., Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - HR1234 - amendment to Internal Revenue Code, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - HR1235 - increased penalties for sale of narcotics to persons under 21, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - H Res.242 - amendment to House of Representatives Rule #XI, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - HR1236 - amendment to Social Security Act, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - HR13 - permit individuals entitled to old-age benefits to earn $100 per month without deductions from their benefits, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - HR1237 - amendment to Civil Service Act, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - HR1238 - abolish free transmission of official government mail, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - HR1239 - no benefits to felons, Date Unknown (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Assorted legislation, Date Unknown
    - Miscellaneous legislation, Date Unknown (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous legislation, Date Unknown (Box 40)
  - Military Related Materials, Date Unknown
    - Veterans A-H, Date Unknown (Box 7)
    - Veterans I-Z, Date Unknown (Box 8)
    - Military A-G, Date Unknown (Box 9)
    - Military H-M, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Military N-Z, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Academies A-C, Date Unknown (Box 15)
    - Academies D-J, Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - Academies J-Se, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Academies Sl-Z, Date Unknown (Box 18)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1954, 1952-1954
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1954, 1952-1954 (Box 41)
  - Questionnaire, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 1-12)
  - Congressional Record offprint - Questionnaire Results, Date Unknown (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Replies to Jan. Letter, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - County Committee Lists, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - County Committee Lists, Date Unknown (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Hall Campaign, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 17-18)
  - Hall File, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Hall Clippings, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Hall-Frank Violation, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Hall-Frank Violation, Date Unknown (Box 42, Folder 22-23)
  - Spotlight, Date Unknown (Box 42, Folder 24-27)
  - District Election Returns, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Political (Corres.), 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Hall, Date Unknown (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Interview by Charles T. Morrissey, Date Unknown (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Letter sent Broome Co. Committee over Foley's signature with editorial about Mr. Cole in Binghamton Press, Date Unknown (Box 42)
- Assorted Files, 1935-1954
  Personal business; Campaigns and Elections; Flood Relief; W.F. Willcox; etc.
  - Personal business, Date Unknown (Box 1)
  - Personal business; flood control, Date Unknown (Box 2)
  - Willcox, W. F. (general file), Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Elmira College, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller General, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dwight Eisenhower Campaign '52 Misc. '52-'54, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Committee - 77th, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tompkins County Flood Relief 1935, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chemung County Flood Relief 1935, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Steuben County Flood Relief 1935, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Tioga County Flood Relief 1935, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Schuyler County Flood Relief 1935, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Damages - 1935, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Flood Relief Photographs, etc.
  - Finger Lakes Wine Growers, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Birthday (messages received by Cole 1953), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pres. Poll, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - General file, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Whip (Republican) 74th Congress 1st session, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Endorsements 1936, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Campaign 1936, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Convention 1936, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 19)